&gt；&gt；Kyle：练习二要求你做与我们在练习中做的完全相同的事情
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Exercise two calls for you to do the exact same thing as we did in exercise
一，除了现在我们要用雷管，好吗？
one, except now we're gonna use thunks, okay?
所以如果你在EX2中打开Read Me，我们有完全相同的设置。
So if you open up the Read Me in the EX2, we have the exact same set up.
对你来说应该是一样的。
Should look the same to you.
没有不同的复杂性。
No complexities different.
但就是这一行，我代码中的第23行。
But it is this line right here, line 23 in my code.
这就是我想引起你注意的。
That's the one I want to call your attention to.
getFile函数是thunk构造函数。
The getFile function is your thunk constructor.
GetFile需要生成thunk。
GetFile needs to produce a thunk.
问题是，你的thunk应该是懒惰的，还是应该是活跃的？
The question is, should your thunk be lazy, or should your thunk be active?
如果你的思维是懒惰的，我们会要求
If your thunk is lazy, are we going to be asking for
文件并行是不是我们想要的方式？
files in parallel the way we want to or not?
如果你的thunk是活跃的，会要求他们并行吗？
If your thunk is active, will be asking for them in parallel?
好的，所以第一个任务，弄清楚怎么做。
Okay, so first task, figure out how to make the thunk.
第二个任务，你可能真的想以相反的顺序完成这些任务，
And second task, which you may actually want to do these in reverse order,
就是弄清楚我要如何使用这些东西来排序他们的输出？
is figure out how am I going to use those things to sequence their outputs?
所以我给你五个。
So I'll give you five.
让我们就八分钟来玩弄这个特技吧。
Let's call it eight minutes to play around with the stunt.
记住我们这里没有使用任何图书馆，
Remember we're not using any libraries here,
我们只是简单地以不同的方式在闭包中使用函数的概念。
we're just simply using the notions of function in closure in a different way.
这里不需要任何全局变量。
You're not gonna need any global variables here.
所以如果你沿着练习一所做的路线走下去，你就太难了。
So if you go down the route you did in exercise one, you're doing it too hard.
我们看看你能想到什么。
We'll see what you come up with.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：快速问题。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Quick question.
他们问你是否跳过幻灯片40。
They're asking if you go over slide 40.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：我确实看了40张幻灯片。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: I did go over slide 40.
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：再说一遍，但你复习了吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Again, but did you review it?
&gt；&gt；Kyle：是的，我看过了。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Yes I did review.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的，对不起。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay sorry.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：我可以再看一遍。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: I can review it one more time.
在第七行中创建的函数是硬编码的
The function created in line seven is hard coded to know
addAsync函数就是它将要调用的函数。
that the addAsync function is what it's going to call.
它还知道它将要传递的三个东西中的两个。
And it also knows two of the three things that it's gonna pass in.
它知道它会通过10分和15分，
It knows that it's going to pass in a ten and a 15,
但它不知道它将传入什么回调。
but it doesn't know what callback it's going to pass in.
所以它很难编码知道addAsync和10和15，它正在等待
So it's hard coded to know addAsync and ten and 15, and it's waiting for
要参数化的回调。
callback to be parameterized.
我们将第11行上的回调参数化。
We parameterize that call back on line 11.
我们回传了一个电话给那个家伙。
We passed in a call back to that thunk.
这就是用ten、15和调用addAsync函数的原因
That is what invokes the addAsync function with ten, 15, and
我们传入的回调。
the callback we passed in.
第二行设置超时，
Line two sets up a timeout,
在一千毫秒之后，它调用传入的回调。
and after a thousand milliseconds it calls the callback passed in.
传入10和15相加的值，
Passing in the values that are at the addition of ten and 15,
值为25。
which is the value 25.
然后返回到第11行，参数sum的值为25。
Which then comes back to line 11, the parameter sum has the value of 25.